

João Paulo Dias de Almeida

Researcher/Developer

Personal

Name	João Paulo Dias de Almeida
Birthday	07/10/1988
Nationality	Brazilian
Language	English,Portuguese

Contact

Phone	+55 75 992315279
Mail	joao.dias@ufba.br
Address	Salvador,Bahia

Skills

- Java
- Python
- C
- R for Statistical Analysis
- SPARQL
- OWL Web Ontology Language

Interests









ABOUT ME

João Paulo Almeida currently is an admitted Ph.D. candidate in Computer Science, at the Federal University of Bahia, Salvador, Brazil. He received his M.Sc in Applied Computing and Computer Engineering degree from State University of Feira de Santana, Feira de Santana, Brazil. He has worked as Professor in Adventist college of Bahia, lectured in Database, Computer Architecture, and Operational Systems. His areas of interests are Semantic Web, Information Retrieval, Spatial Queries, and Databases.

EDUCATION

Universidade Federal da Bahia

2016

Universidade Estadual de Feira de Santana

2013-2015

Universidade Estadual de Feira de Santana

2006-2012

Ph.D. in progress in Computer Science

Advisor: Frederico Araújo Durão Grantee of: FAPESB, Bahia, Brasil

Master's in Applied Computing

Advisor: João Batista da Rocha Júnior

Grantee of: CAPES, Brasil

Graduation in Computer Engineering

Advisor: Ana Lucia Lima Marreiros Maia

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Faculdade Adventista da Bahia

2016-2019

SENAI Feira de Santana

> 2016 2012

Centro Estadual de Educação **Áureo FIlho**

2013

ECOMP JR. - UEFS 2008-2012

Professor

Databases I and II, Operational Systems Applied Logic, Computer Architecture

Technical Instructor

Databases (2016)

C applied to Microprocessors (2012)

Technical Instructor

Logic for Programing Introduction to Computer Science

Advisor Member (2010-2012) Quality and HR Director (2008-2009)